

RONALDO CHERUIYOT

Software Engineer

About Me

I am a dedicated software engineer and full-stack developer who consistently goes above and beyond to assist those in need, demonstrating both technical expertise and a compassionate nature in my work.



+254-719-252-546



ronaldokipkirui90@gmail.com



Nairobi, Kenya



https://github.com/Roro1839



ronaldo-cheruiyot-059939266/

LANGUAGE

- ₽ython
- Clanguage
- Html
- Javascript
- SQL

EXPERTISE

- Tech Skills
- Creativity
- •//Helpfulness
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

EXPERIENCE

Litein Liquor Shop Litein - Kenya Apr 2023 - Aug 2023

Basically I worked their since April - September

Korongo Liberty Gospel Church Youth Representative Litein - Kenya, Jan 2017 - present

EDUCATION

ALX SE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING specialized in Back-end November 2022-Dec 2023

Cheborge Boys High School

High School Diploma May 2021-April 2022

KCA University

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN APPLIED COMPUTING
Sep 2022- current there

SKILLS SUMMARY

Leadership

Tech Management

Software Engineering

Full stack / Back-end

78 %

81 %

81 %